



+34 602 34 20 03



yulibeth.rivero@gmail.com



in/yulibeth-rivero/



https://github.com/Yul1b3th



https://yul1b3th.github.io

Tech skills

Front End: Angular, Vue, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, jQuery, Jest.

Back End: Nest, MySQL, PHP (Mainly used in WordPress, PrestaShop, Magento).

Design: Photoshop, Illustrator,

Adobe XD, InDesign.

Others: Scrum, Git, GitHub,

Postman.

Soft skills

Autonomy
Goal Orientation
Teamwork
Customer Orientation
Flexibility and Change Management

Languages

Spanish: Native English: B2 Catalan: B2

> Total Availability Immediate Incorporation

Yulibeth Rivero

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

Since 2016, I have been working in web development, using a variety of technologies in both design and frontend and backend development. My constant motivation is to stay updated on the latest trends and advancements in web development.



EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

IT Academy - Barcelona Activa | 2024 - Present | Spain Project ITA Challenges

- Implement new interactive features and perform testing with Jest.
- Test APIs to retrieve specific data and functionalities using Postman.
- Collaborate in task management and progress tracking on GitHub.
- Repository: Frontend

Final Bootcamp Sprint Project

- Design and develop an application for room rentals by geolocation using Angular, Nest, MySQL, and Mapbox.
- Demo: Visit the demo
- Repositories: Frontend | Backend

Front End Developer

Grupo Anaya, S.A.U. | 2023 (Temporary - 6 months) | Spain

- Adapt printed content from primary and secondary education books to web formats.
- Design and develop games with JavaScript for interactive books.

Web Designer

Principios Interactivos S.L. | 2019 - 2022 | Spain

- Design and layout digital campaigns for CaixaBank Digital.
- Load and send campaign tests with Adobe Campaign.

Web Developer

VIP Rental Barcelona, S.L.U. | 2016 - 2019 | Spain

- Maintain, update, and layout websites in WordPress, PrestaShop, and Magento.
- Design, layout, and publish digital campaigns.

Owner

Freelance | Intercid C.A. | 2007 - 2014 | Venezuela

- Manage e-commerce for technological devices.
- Teach basic computing to children, teenagers, and adults.

EDUCATION

Front End Web Developer with Angular

IT Academy - Barcelona Activa | 2024 | Spain

• 350-hour bootcamp.

Front End Web Developer with Vue

La Salle Universidad Ramon Llull | 2023 | Spain

• 240-hour bootcamp.

Front End Web Developer with Vue

Eurecat | 2022 | Spain

• 240-hour bootcamp.

Level 2 Professional Certification

Web Page Creation and Publication | CIFO | 2016 | Spain

• 560 hours.

Computer Engineer

Universidad "Fermín Toro" | 2004 | Venezuela

• 5 years.